Sean Chaucer Levine (908-285-5179) sean@ghostmouth.com Minneapolis, MN

Experienced Web Developer, Educator, and Audio Engineer with great communication skills. Excels at debugging, team oriented full stack web development, and front-end design. Obsessed with troubleshooting, digesting new information, and creating iconic content. Knowledgeable and experienced at implementing a variety of different database languages, and a proficient performer and educator of over twelve musical instruments.

Portfolio: http://www.seanchaucerlevine.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-levine-a803a239/

Github: https://github.com/Ghostmouth

Projects

Task Manager | https://github.com/hallek7/Titanic-float-none | https://guarded-sea-37827.herokuapp.com/ Server Routes & Front End

Integrates a SQL database with a task management database to store user information, project information, tasks, and deadlines. Utilizes mySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Sequelize, HTML5, CSS, node, JS, and Express.

News Scraper | https://github.com/Ghostmouth/newsscraper | https://mongoose-hwassignment.herokuapp.com/ | Full Stack Development

Scrapes news articles from NPR, with functionality to save and store articles, and comments to a mongo database. Utilizes mongoDB, mongoose, JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, CSS, and node.JS.

Band Website | https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite |
https://github.com/Ghostmouth/ghostmouthwebsite |
https://www.ghostmouth.com

Full Stack Development

Website for a Minneapolis music project. Utilizes JavaScript, handlebars, HTML, and CSS.

Professional Experience

Minneapolis Public Schools- Reserve Teacher

- Filled in for elementary, middle, and high school teachers at many schools in the Minneapolis Public School district
- Frequently sought after to fill music, technology, and other specialized positions within the district

September 2017- Present

Teachers On Call- Reserve Teacher

• Filled in for Paraprofessional Educators at a variety of different schools in the 916 District, Hopkins, and St. Paul School Systems, with particular focus on schools that specialize in Emotional Behavior Disorders, and Autism

January 2016- Present

Cause Spirits and Soundbar- Web Developer

- Updated, maintained, and debugged the venue's website
- Implemented a SQL database for the venue's event calendar
- Integrated the website with the venue's various social media pages
- Helped advise the management of the venue on how to increase the establishment's search engine optimization

Spring 2013- July 2014

Banana Static-Web Manager, Public Relations, Content Creator

- Developed, designed, and maintained the website for a Minneapolis Entertainment Web Site that saw some popularity as a music review site
- Maintained email contact and accepted submissions from various publishing companies, record labels, and management teams
- Contributed content to the website

January 2010- June 2012

331- Security

- In charge of managing and training the security staff of the club, ensuring the safety of the staff, and patrons during a variety of different of events that the club hosted
- Helped manage the security team during the Art-A-Whirl event of 2013, 2014, 2015, 2016, 2017, and 2018

Spring 2013- Present

Technical Skills

- Computer Technologies: Javascript, Java, Swift, React.js, jQuery, Node.js, Firebase, MySQL, MongoDB, AJAX, Python,
- Audio Workstations: Experience in Analog Recording and Digital Audio Workstations (Logic Pro, Protools, Harrison Mixbus)
- Visual Editing Suites: Photoshop, ImageGlitch, iMovie, Microsoft Office
- Musical Instruments: Piano, Trumpet, Trombone, Flute, Guitar, Saxophone, Synthesizer, Percussion, Double Bass, Clarinet

Education

University of Minnesota- Certificate in Web Development

Expected Graduation October 2018

McNally Smith College of Music- Bachelor of Music in Performance

Graduated Spring 2012